[Music]
anyway besides all that now the next bit
of the video and at the potential and
insurance office blocks I'm going to
have a way look around here I have to
find out about parking while there's
nothing going on but I'll
uh get something sorted we get some
footage of this building so this is the
main entrance to it it's just a stone
throw away from sterland really you
could still hear the motor where in fact
you could see it from the motor that's I
was I was noticing that over the years a
number of times them down the motorway
you know I noticed the building never
thought a lot of it like until I noticed
it was abandoned and I said
oh because I've done videos before on
abandoned buildings and stuff and I
thought well this might be interesting
so I'll get myself here seen at this
seen an out traveling around I thought
well might as well come in this way
today and uh get some
footage so it is on the there a lovely
Lake
river that one long that we not sure
what it's called
but i' have to look on the map or
something so it's uh in it's Craig
fourth uh Business
Park where
is is at it looks some of the buildings
have been de demolished already
unfortunately
would to get some footage of it even
being demolished would have been
interesting there's no what being done
today I don't think being a bank holiday
Monday and it's in a lovely bit of the
area lovely we bit of scenting that
looks quite nice you know it's nice
it's no bad area lovely
bit having your office next to
that
yeah so I'm presuming so I'm presuming
this will be like
the the main car part over there oh here
we go there's a bit more of the building
before this all G
so I can hear the generators
running for all the demolition stuff so
there is quite a considerable M that's
going already
unfortunately um I wish I had the chance
and opportunity to get inside that bton
you know before it was getting
demolished because I've seen like a
video but I saw a video titled an
exploration video so obviously look at
this
um luckily enough managed to get
in yeah that's one thing I never do I
never uh I never break into any BS if
the BS are open already or if it's a
door open or something then then I could
I could go in I wouldn't I wouldn't
break me I wouldn't break an enter I
would never do that but on Old buildings
and stuff that I've thought on videos uh
adventures and Explorations the doors
that have already been open
and I would have wished I could have
took the opportunity to get in here if
there were a door open or something
because it looks like it's already had
Explorations done seen a video title
wish as a year I could have done that
but too late
unfortunately this is all I could do I
just show what there
is from here basically
this building was massive I
mean I saw from the motorway and it
really did stand out quite a lot you
know it was a major
building big office blocks and
was stood up quite a
bit it's completely gr over
a
St a be or something
f p
out B Be FL it
th the cliffs up there as well which
is quite something see if we can get
myself right round it uh the view right
around
see if we could walk right around
so I've kind of like came to the end of
the car park and it's not bad bit of the
countryside
uh the building's just up there on the
right so I'm not quite sure just how
have I could even get around this build
I'm not sure where this path or nature
trail leads
to obviously it must lead to the road I
presume but I don't know just how far
I've got to go to get to it I know I'm
going to be walking for a few
miles it's quite a long I don't I want
to go B huge DET I want to get around
the building you know footage from the
motorway side but I normally used to see
see I drive that road um it's nice nice
Pond down there
so I just not quite sure the motorway is
up there you might see the traffic just
through
the you might see the moving traffic
well that's the main that's the
M9 so I just didn't again how much
further obviously the traffic get into
the place must come in from M ja coming
from where in pared and this might be
way another way get that butterfly uh
right this looks like it's going to go
for nah no forget it I change of mind
I'm not going to go any further down
that direction because I could we to we
end up at Tim too I'm going to go back
the way I came and I'll just walk back
around the front from the other side I
thought it was going to be easy getting
around there but certain it doesn't look
like it B clicking that could go in for
ages and I know going further I'm just
going to go back to where I came and I
just get on the front from the other
side just want to show you this this
looks really nice that's a nice view
that
just thought I'd capture that moment for
you and Sterling's over that way the
Sterling Castle is all that way as well
Wallace monument is also not over far
from the castle
is
so up towards the
circle uh with the motorways that's like
the main entrance into
there say it's just off the main road so
way we going out to off the M9 not the
A9 it's the main round the B and the
entrance to the place is
just so see if we can get a footage
toward Wass the looking in the M site so
as long as I'm behind that barrier and
just getting the footage from there
looking in that's how you would see it
from the road basically
so let's just look at it from here um
it's a little bit awkward to get down to
that I don't really want to have to go
down there it just looks rather awkward
but I'll see I'll see might I'll just
have a think of that I don't really want
to go down that but I the side of the
barrier by the way so I'm
not
do awkward
so I've got myself closer to it the
building uh it's under demolition at the
moment however I'm just going to have a
look around here and see what's just
around the corner and see if we can get
some
footage hopefully closer
[Applause]
so I'm just getting a bit of footage
from up here as well
uh of the the old buildings and
then after that I'll going have to go
sh
so that's just
[Music]
part for
oh
for
[Music]
I
for
well got some bonus footage there for
you
um as I say I got bonus footage but
that's i w there was a way in and I
didn't I don't break an enter so that's
just I make that very clear I do not
break and Enter and I know it's a
dangerous and I went into my own
visk
so anyway
right so that's that done
um got footage inside
um so roll off the video it's been quite
a long video quite a long day for me
actually I've got about a 50 m drive
back to dundy but I've got to do
something when I get back so I'm going
have to get chapped on
basically uh I'll make it right see what
else put on my channel uh thanks for
watching and hope you enjoyed it hey
chill out bye for no bye
[Music]